[
  {
    "Question" : "Which word describes you better?",
    "Answer" : "Intense",
    "Choice 1" : "Intense",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Intense",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How important is religion/God in your life?",
    "Answer" : "Not important at all",
    "Choice 1" : "Somewhat important",
    "Choice 2" : "Not very important",
    "Choice 3" : "Not important at all",
    "Prefer 1" : "Not important at all",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy discussing politics?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Is astrological sign at all important in a match?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you date someone who was in considerable debt?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, if I thought the debt were justified",
    "Choice 2" : "No",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Could you date someone who was really messy?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How frequently do you drink alcohol?",
    "Answer" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 1" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 2" : "Rarely",
    "Choice 3" : "Never",
    "Prefer 1" : "Often",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which event sounds most appealing?",
    "Answer" : "Music Festival",
    "Choice 1" : "Political Convention",
    "Choice 2" : "Music Festival",
    "Choice 3" : "New Years Eve in Times Square",
    "Prefer 1" : "Music Festival",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you like scary movies?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How often are you open with your feelings?",
    "Answer" : "Always",
    "Choice 1" : "Usually",
    "Choice 2" : "Rarely",
    "Choice 3" : "Never",
    "Prefer 1" : "Always",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Could you date someone who does drugs?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, but only soft stuff like marijuana",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, but only soft stuff like marijuana",
    "Choice 2" : "Yes",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, but only soft stuff like marijuana",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you often find yourself worrying about things that you have no control over?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Is smoking disgusting?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do spelling mistakes annoy you?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you either vegetarian or vegan?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Is art important to you?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you like the taste of beer?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you a workaholic?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you like using party drugs like MDMA/molly?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, but rarely",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, but rarely",
    "Choice 2" : "Nope, not at all",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "About how long do you want your next relationship to last?",
    "Answer" : "A few months to a year",
    "Choice 1" : "A few months to a year",
    "Choice 2" : "Several years",
    "Choice 3" : "The rest of my life",
    "Prefer 1" : "One night",
    "Prefer 2" : "A few months to a year",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you ready to settle down and get married right now?",
    "Answer" : "No way",
    "Choice 1" : "No way",
    "Choice 2" : "Get married yes, settle down no",
    "Choice 3" : "Get married no, settle down yes",
    "Prefer 1" : "No way",
    "Prefer 2" : "Get married no, settle down yes",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Regardless of future plans, what's more interesting to you right now?",
    "Answer" : "Love",
    "Choice 1" : "Love",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How willing are you to meet someone from OkCupid in person?",
    "Answer" : "Totally willing!",
    "Choice 1" : "Hesitant, but I'd certainly consider it.",
    "Choice 2" : "I'm not interested in meeting in person.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Totally willing!",
    "Prefer 2" : "Hesitant, but I'd certainly consider it.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which best describes your political beliefs?",
    "Answer" : "Other",
    "Choice 1" : "Centrist",
    "Choice 2" : "Conservative / Right-wing",
    "Choice 3" : "Other",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which would you rather be?",
    "Answer" : "Normal",
    "Choice 1" : "Weird",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "In a relationship, who do you prefer to be taller?",
    "Answer" : "I like to be taller.",
    "Choice 1" : "I like my partner to be taller.",
    "Choice 2" : "I like us to be about the same height.",
    "Choice 3" : "It doesn't matter to me.",
    "Prefer 1" : "I like my partner to be taller.",
    "Prefer 2" : "I like us to be about the same height.",
    "Prefer 3" : "It doesn't matter to me.",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Say you've started seeing someone you really like. As far as you're concerned, how long will it take before you have sex?",
    "Answer" : "3-5 dates",
    "Choice 1" : "3-5 dates",
    "Choice 2" : "6 or more dates",
    "Choice 3" : "Only after the wedding",
    "Prefer 1" : "1-2 dates",
    "Prefer 2" : "3-5 dates",
    "Prefer 3" : "6 or more dates",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Can you tell from someone’s dating profile whether or not you’ll get along in real life?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "About half the time",
    "Choice 2" : "No, usually",
    "Choice 3" : "I don't know",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Rate your self-confidence:",
    "Answer" : "Higher than average",
    "Choice 1" : "Higher than average",
    "Choice 2" : "Average",
    "Choice 3" : "Below average",
    "Prefer 1" : "Higher than average",
    "Prefer 2" : "Average",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How important is money/wealth for you in a match?",
    "Answer" : "Somewhat important",
    "Choice 1" : "Somewhat important",
    "Choice 2" : "Not important at all",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Very important",
    "Prefer 2" : "Somewhat important",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "What is the most exciting thing about getting to know someone new?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "Discovering their body",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which makes for a better relationship?",
    "Answer" : "Passion",
    "Choice 1" : "Dedication",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy intense intellectual conversations?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Is jealousy healthy in a relationship?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you prefer good things happened, or interesting things?",
    "Answer" : "Interesting",
    "Choice 1" : "Interesting",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you consider yourself a feminist?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "To some extent",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "To some extent",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you a cat person or a dog person?",
    "Answer" : "Both",
    "Choice 1" : "Dogs",
    "Choice 2" : "Both",
    "Choice 3" : "Neither",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Have you ever traveled around another country alone?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which of the following types of intelligence do you value most?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "Social / Interpersonal",
    "Choice 2" : "Visual / Artistic",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "What's your relationship with marijuana?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "I smoke occasionally.",
    "Choice 2" : "I smoked in the past, but no longer.",
    "Choice 3" : "Never.",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "What's your deal with harder drugs (stuff beyond pot)?",
    "Answer" : "I do drugs occasionally.",
    "Choice 1" : "I do drugs occasionally.",
    "Choice 2" : "I've done drugs in the past, but no longer.",
    "Choice 3" : "I never do drugs.",
    "Prefer 1" : "I do drugs occasionally.",
    "Prefer 2" : "I never do drugs.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Should evolution and creationism be taught side-by-side in school?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, students should hear both sides",
    "Choice 1" : "No, creationism has no place in schools",
    "Choice 2" : "No, evolution has no place in schools",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "For you personally, is abortion an option in case of an accidental pregnancy?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "What is the longest you've traveled to meet up with someone from a dating app?",
    "Answer" : "Between one and five hours",
    "Choice 1" : "Between one and five hours",
    "Choice 2" : "More than five hours",
    "Choice 3" : "I've never met up with someone from a dating app",
    "Prefer 1" : "Less than an hour",
    "Prefer 2" : "Between one and five hours",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Once you're intimate, how often would you and your significant other have sex?",
    "Answer" : "Once or twice a week",
    "Choice 1" : "About every other day",
    "Choice 2" : "Once or twice a week",
    "Choice 3" : "A few times a month or less",
    "Prefer 1" : "Every day",
    "Prefer 2" : "About every other day",
    "Prefer 3" : "Once or twice a week",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "If you don't do anything at all for an entire day, how does that make you feel?",
    "Answer" : "Bad",
    "Choice 1" : "Bad",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you need to sleep with someone before you considered marrying them?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you consider sleeping with someone on the first date?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Could you date someone who was really quiet?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How often do you keep your promises?",
    "Answer" : "Always",
    "Choice 1" : "Whenever possible",
    "Choice 2" : "Usually",
    "Choice 3" : "When convenient",
    "Prefer 1" : "Always",
    "Prefer 2" : "Whenever possible",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Is it a requirement that you communicate every day with your significant other (via phone, text, in person, whatever)?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, unless otherwise specified",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, unless otherwise specified",
    "Choice 2" : "No, it's not necessary",
    "Choice 3" : "No, I'd prefer not to communicate daily",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, no matter what",
    "Prefer 2" : "Yes, unless otherwise specified",
    "Prefer 3" : "No, it's not necessary",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which of these is likely to make you more nervous?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "An important interview",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you often make jokes that offend more uptight people?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "What is your preferred cuddling position?",
    "Answer" : "Big spoon",
    "Choice 1" : "Small spoon",
    "Choice 2" : "All spoons",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Small spoon",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Could you date someone who already has children from a previous relationship?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you open to a casual relationship (i.e. more than a hookup, less than a significant other)?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, I'm open to casual",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, but only if my partner were reliable",
    "Choice 2" : "No",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, I'm open to casual",
    "Prefer 2" : "No",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How do you feel about documentaries?",
    "Answer" : "Okay",
    "Choice 1" : "Okay",
    "Choice 2" : "NO.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yay!",
    "Prefer 2" : "Okay",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "If you had to name your greatest motivation in life thus far, what would it be?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "Wealth",
    "Choice 2" : "Expression",
    "Choice 3" : "Knowledge",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you kinky?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "A bit",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "A bit",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you share your streaming platform passwords with other people?",
    "Answer" : "Of course!",
    "Choice 1" : "Only if they split the cost",
    "Choice 2" : "I only use other people’s passwords",
    "Choice 3" : "No, I don't share",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "What do you do when a new season of your favorite Netflix show drops?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "Binge it with multiple breaks",
    "Choice 2" : "Watch it slowly to make it last",
    "Choice 3" : "I didn’t even know there was a new season",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you a good trivia team member?",
    "Answer" : "I hate trivia",
    "Choice 1" : "Only for certain topics",
    "Choice 2" : "No, please help me",
    "Choice 3" : "I hate trivia",
    "Prefer 1" : "Only for certain topics",
    "Prefer 2" : "No, please help me",
    "Prefer 3" : "I hate trivia",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you a coffee snob?",
    "Answer" : "Not really, I’ll drink anything",
    "Choice 1" : "Not really, I’ll drink anything",
    "Choice 2" : "I don’t drink coffee",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Not really, I’ll drink anything",
    "Prefer 2" : "I don’t drink coffee",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "It’s your first date. Do you split the bill, pay the whole bill, have them pay the whole bill",
    "Answer" : "It doesn't matter to me",
    "Choice 1" : "Pay the whole bill",
    "Choice 2" : "Have them pay the whole bill",
    "Choice 3" : "It doesn't matter to me",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you believe morality is universal, or relative?",
    "Answer" : "Relative",
    "Choice 1" : "Relative",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you break up with someone if you found out they were micro-cheating (small acts, like secretly texting an ex, that imply they're emotionally or physically interested in someone else)?",
    "Answer" : "It depends on the circumstances",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "It depends on the circumstances",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "It depends on the circumstances",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you still order off the kids menu?",
    "Answer" : "No, I am an adult",
    "Choice 1" : "Once in a while",
    "Choice 2" : "No, I am an adult",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No, I am an adult",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How do you feel about TV reboots?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "ENOUGH",
    "Choice 2" : "Only if it’s for a show I like",
    "Choice 3" : "I’m indifferent",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you like writing lists?",
    "Answer" : "1. Yes 2. Yes! 3. YES",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "1. Yes 2. Yes! 3. YES",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Is a hotdog a sandwich?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you consider having an open relationship (i.e., one where you can see other people)?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you think \"hey\" is a good first message to receive on a dating app?",
    "Answer" : "No, please be a little more creative than that",
    "Choice 1" : "It should at least be \"Hey, what's up?",
    "Choice 2" : "No, please be a little more creative than that",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "What's your Hogwarts house?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "Hufflepuff",
    "Choice 2" : "Ravenclaw",
    "Choice 3" : "Slytherin",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "I would rather vote for a candidate whose policies significantly:",
    "Answer" : "Benefitted the majority of society more than me",
    "Choice 1" : "Benefitted the majority of society more than me",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Benefitted the majority of society more than me",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Should we be fighting to close the gender wage gap?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "It's not top priority",
    "Choice 2" : "What wage gap?",
    "Choice 3" : "I don't care",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you think the US government unfairly over-incarcerates people of color?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "Maybe, but I stand by what's decided in each case",
    "Choice 2" : "No, it does not",
    "Choice 3" : "I'm not sure",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would an immigration ban that targets Muslims make the country safer?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "Maybe, but we shouldn't enforce one",
    "Choice 2" : "No",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Maybe, but we shouldn't enforce one",
    "Prefer 2" : "No",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you think the military should ban transgender people from service?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes",
    "Choice 2" : "I'm not sure",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "I'm not sure",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you think people who have entered the country illegally should be deported?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, all of them",
    "Choice 1" : "Some of them",
    "Choice 2" : "No, none of them",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, all of them",
    "Prefer 2" : "Some of them",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Should governments be allowed to censor the media in order to protect their citizens?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you turn your phone off at the movies?",
    "Answer" : "I put it on silent or airplane mode",
    "Choice 1" : "I put it on silent or airplane mode",
    "Choice 2" : "No, but I put it away",
    "Choice 3" : "No, I still use it",
    "Prefer 1" : "Of course, I’m not a monster",
    "Prefer 2" : "I put it on silent or airplane mode",
    "Prefer 3" : "No, but I put it away",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you tag your friends in memes?",
    "Answer" : "Yes!",
    "Choice 1" : "No, it’s annoying",
    "Choice 2" : "What’s a meme?",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes!",
    "Prefer 2" : "No, it’s annoying",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Should abortion be legal?",
    "Answer" : "Absolutely",
    "Choice 1" : "Absolutely not",
    "Choice 2" : "Sometimes, it depends",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you consider dating someone who has no interest in sex and experiences no sexual attraction?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Marvel or DC?",
    "Answer" : "What’s the difference?",
    "Choice 1" : "DC, all the way",
    "Choice 2" : "They’re both great",
    "Choice 3" : "What’s the difference?",
    "Prefer 1" : "They’re both great",
    "Prefer 2" : "What’s the difference?",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you be upset if your partner sat on someone else's lap?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "What’s the most exhausting/annoying part about dating?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "The lack of chivalry",
    "Choice 2" : "The same kinds of dates (drinks or coffee) over an",
    "Choice 3" : "I never find it exhausting or annoying",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you think it’s important to challenge typical gender roles in dating?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you consider dating someone who has vocalized a strong negative bias toward a certain race of people?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you ever Skype/call/video chat a date you met online before meeting up in person?",
    "Answer" : "Maybe, if someone asked me to",
    "Choice 1" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 2" : "Maybe, if someone asked me to",
    "Choice 3" : "Never",
    "Prefer 1" : "Maybe, if someone asked me to",
    "Prefer 2" : "Never",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Should burning your country's flag be illegal?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you believe your country would be more or less safe if every adult owned a gun?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "Less safe",
    "Choice 2" : "Neither / unsure",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you a morning person?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you believe contraception is morally wrong?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How often do you brush your teeth?",
    "Answer" : "Twice or more a day",
    "Choice 1" : "Once a day",
    "Choice 2" : "Only on days I feel like it",
    "Choice 3" : "Rarely / never",
    "Prefer 1" : "Twice or more a day",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you space out or daydream a lot?",
    "Answer" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 1" : "Rarely / never",
    "Choice 2" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Rarely / never",
    "Prefer 2" : "Sometimes",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which of these options most closely describes what you're looking for in your next relationship?",
    "Answer" : "Someone to go out with",
    "Choice 1" : "Someone to go out with",
    "Choice 2" : "Someone for tonight",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Someone to come home to",
    "Prefer 2" : "Someone to go out with",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you date someone who did not support the #MeToo movement?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How important are your political beliefs to you?",
    "Answer" : "Not at all important",
    "Choice 1" : "Somewhat important",
    "Choice 2" : "A little important",
    "Choice 3" : "Not at all important",
    "Prefer 1" : "Somewhat important",
    "Prefer 2" : "A little important",
    "Prefer 3" : "Not at all important",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Is intelligence a turn on?",
    "Answer" : "Yes!",
    "Choice 1" : "Somewhat.",
    "Choice 2" : "Intelligence does nothing for me either way.",
    "Choice 3" : "Intelligence turns me off.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes!",
    "Prefer 2" : "Somewhat.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you need a creative outlet (to play an instrument, paint, write, etc)?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, I need a way to express myself",
    "Choice 1" : "Sometimes, but I could live without it",
    "Choice 2" : "I'm fine without one",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, I need a way to express myself",
    "Prefer 2" : "Sometimes, but I could live without it",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Have you ever had a sexual encounter with someone of the same sex?",
    "Answer" : "No, and I would never.",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, and I did not enjoy myself.",
    "Choice 2" : "No, and I would never.",
    "Choice 3" : "No, but I would like to.",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you looking for a partner to have children with?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How often do you use social media?",
    "Answer" : "I'm a somewhat active user.",
    "Choice 1" : "I'm a somewhat active user.",
    "Choice 2" : "I rarely use it.",
    "Choice 3" : "I never use it.",
    "Prefer 1" : "I'm a very active user.",
    "Prefer 2" : "I'm a somewhat active user.",
    "Prefer 3" : "I rarely use it.",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Have you ever fantasized about hooking up with a co-worker?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, and I have not acted on it",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, and I have not acted on it",
    "Choice 2" : "No",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you an aspiring actor/artist/writer or other creative type?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which superpower would you rather have?",
    "Answer" : "Flight",
    "Choice 1" : "Invisibility",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How long do your romantic relationships usually last?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "6-12 months",
    "Choice 2" : "12+ months",
    "Choice 3" : "I've never been in a relationship",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you think statues and streets named after confederate generals should be removed or changed?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "I don't care",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "What’s the best part of dating?",
    "Answer" : "The sex",
    "Choice 1" : "The actual dates",
    "Choice 2" : "The sex",
    "Choice 3" : "Having someone to take as your plus-one",
    "Prefer 1" : "The sex",
    "Prefer 2" : "Having someone to take as your plus-one",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which is bigger?",
    "Answer" : "The Sun",
    "Choice 1" : "The Sun",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Could you be in a committed relationship with someone who regularly smokes pot (> 2 times a week)?\\n",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "Only if it were for medical use",
    "Choice 2" : "No",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "If you were to die, would whoever goes through your personal belongings be shocked by what they find?",
    "Answer" : "No.",
    "Choice 1" : "No.",
    "Choice 2" : "Maybe a little bit.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No.",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you keep a budget of your finances?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How frequently do you bathe or shower?",
    "Answer" : "Usually daily.  I skip some.",
    "Choice 1" : "Usually daily.  I skip some.",
    "Choice 2" : "A couple times a week.",
    "Choice 3" : "Once a week or less.",
    "Prefer 1" : "At least once a day.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Usually daily.  I skip some.",
    "Prefer 3" : "A couple times a week.",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How do you feel about falling in love?",
    "Answer" : "I like to just let it happen",
    "Choice 1" : "I try to avoid it",
    "Choice 2" : "I like to just let it happen",
    "Choice 3" : "I'm indifferent / not sure",
    "Prefer 1" : "I love it and want it very much",
    "Prefer 2" : "I like to just let it happen",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you like to cuddle?",
    "Answer" : "Yes.",
    "Choice 1" : "No.",
    "Choice 2" : "Sometimes - It depends.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Sometimes - It depends.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How open are you to trying new things in bed?",
    "Answer" : "I'm open, but I don't get too crazy.",
    "Choice 1" : "I'm open, but I don't get too crazy.",
    "Choice 2" : "Hesitant, but it might happen.",
    "Choice 3" : "Not at all.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Very open. I'll try anything once.",
    "Prefer 2" : "I'm open, but I don't get too crazy.",
    "Prefer 3" : "Hesitant, but it might happen.",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How much influence or control do your parents have over your life?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "I consider their opinion but go my own way.",
    "Choice 2" : "I almost always do what my parents think is best.",
    "Choice 3" : "I always do what my parents say.",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you—for any reason—read your mate's email or pose as them online, without their knowledge and permission?",
    "Answer" : "No, I'd trust them and that would be invasive.",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, I'd be too curious not to.",
    "Choice 2" : "Only if I suspected them of something.",
    "Choice 3" : "No, I'd trust them and that would be invasive.",
    "Prefer 1" : "No, I'd trust them and that would be invasive.",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you Google someone before a first date?",
    "Answer" : "Yes. Knowledge is power!",
    "Choice 1" : "No. Why spoil the mystery?",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes. Knowledge is power!",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you smarter than most people?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you attracted to dangerous situations?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How important is it to you that your partner smell good?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "Important-ish",
    "Choice 2" : "Less important than you think",
    "Choice 3" : "I just don't care at all",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How long after you've started dating someone do you follow them on social media?",
    "Answer" : "Before we've met in person",
    "Choice 1" : "After the first couple of dates",
    "Choice 2" : "Not until we're in a relationship",
    "Choice 3" : "I'm not into social media",
    "Prefer 1" : "Before we've met in person",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you careful with your money?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How often do you meditate?",
    "Answer" : "Never.",
    "Choice 1" : "Rarely.",
    "Choice 2" : "Never.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Rarely.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Never.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Your significant other's ex is coming into town and he/she wants to go out to dinner with them alone. How do you react?",
    "Answer" : "No way.",
    "Choice 1" : "Not thrilled, but go ahead.",
    "Choice 2" : "No way.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Not thrilled, but go ahead.",
    "Prefer 2" : "No way.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you have a problem with racist jokes?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Should healthcare be funded by the government?",
    "Answer" : "I'm not sure.",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, but only for certain people.",
    "Choice 2" : "No.",
    "Choice 3" : "I'm not sure.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, for everyone.",
    "Prefer 2" : "No.",
    "Prefer 3" : "I'm not sure.",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Should the US build a wall between the US & Mexico?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, but only if Mexico doesn't pay for it",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, but only if Mexico pays for it",
    "Choice 2" : "Yes, but only if Mexico doesn't pay for it",
    "Choice 3" : "100% No",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, no matter what",
    "Prefer 2" : "Yes, but only if Mexico pays for it",
    "Prefer 3" : "Yes, but only if Mexico doesn't pay for it",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How often do you give Facebook updates?",
    "Answer" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 1" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 2" : "Rarely",
    "Choice 3" : "Never",
    "Prefer 1" : "All the time",
    "Prefer 2" : "Sometimes",
    "Prefer 3" : "Rarely",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you ever consider making a sex video with your partner?",
    "Answer" : "Nope, not for me",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, and I'd like to try",
    "Choice 2" : "Nope, not for me",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Nope, not for me",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you Christian?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How do you feel about kids?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "They're okay, but keep the unruly ones at bay.",
    "Choice 2" : "How revolting.",
    "Choice 3" : "I'm indifferent.",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How important is it for you to make physical contact when showing affection for someone?",
    "Answer" : "Very important.",
    "Choice 1" : "Somewhat important.",
    "Choice 2" : "Not important.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Very important.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Somewhat important.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy finding out what makes things work the way they do?",
    "Answer" : "I'm an information sponge",
    "Choice 1" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 2" : "As long as it works, who cares why?",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Have you smoked a cigarette in the last 6 months?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "I prefer to sleep…",
    "Answer" : "Embracing / cuddling my partner",
    "Choice 1" : "With my partner, but apart (not touching)",
    "Choice 2" : "Touching my partner",
    "Choice 3" : "Embracing / cuddling my partner",
    "Prefer 1" : "Touching my partner",
    "Prefer 2" : "Embracing / cuddling my partner",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you believe guns should be allowed in schools?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "Sometimes, it depends",
    "Choice 2" : "No, never",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "In a relationship I like to discuss politics with my partner.",
    "Answer" : "Sure. I'm interested in sharing our beliefs.",
    "Choice 1" : "Sure. I'm interested in sharing our beliefs.",
    "Choice 2" : "Sometimes. It depends.",
    "Choice 3" : "Hardly. Politics are boring or personal.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Sure. I'm interested in sharing our beliefs.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Sometimes. It depends.",
    "Prefer 3" : "Hardly. Politics are boring or personal.",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "What's worse on a first date?",
    "Answer" : "No physical attraction",
    "Choice 1" : "Nothing to talk about",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No physical attraction",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you be okay with your significant other spending a lot of time with one of his/her exes (as a friend)?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How do you think your sex drive compares to what is typical for other people of your age and gender?",
    "Answer" : "My sex drive is higher than average.",
    "Choice 1" : "My sex drive is about average.",
    "Choice 2" : "My sex drive is below average.",
    "Choice 3" : "I'm insatiable.",
    "Prefer 1" : "My sex drive is higher than average.",
    "Prefer 2" : "My sex drive is about average.",
    "Prefer 3" : "I'm insatiable.",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How important is it that your partner be willing and able to participate in meaningful philosophical conversations?",
    "Answer" : "Extremely important.",
    "Choice 1" : "Somewhat important.",
    "Choice 2" : "Not at all important.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Extremely important.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Somewhat important.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Is mansplaining a thing?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, but it’s not a big deal",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, but it’s not a big deal",
    "Choice 2" : "Nope, not a thing",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, but it’s not a big deal",
    "Prefer 2" : "Nope, not a thing",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How are you most likely to show your partner you care?",
    "Answer" : "Actions: Do something nice (like a date or errand)",
    "Choice 1" : "Actions: Do something nice (like a date or errand)",
    "Choice 2" : "Gifts: Buy them flowers, jewelry or a new gadget",
    "Choice 3" : "Touch: Give them a hug, massage or kiss",
    "Prefer 1" : "Words: Tell them how much you appreciate them",
    "Prefer 2" : "Actions: Do something nice (like a date or errand)",
    "Prefer 3" : "Touch: Give them a hug, massage or kiss",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How many children would you ideally like to have?",
    "Answer" : "1/2/18",
    "Choice 1" : "1/2/18",
    "Choice 2" : "3/4/18",
    "Choice 3" : "5 or more!",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Can anything be made the subject of a joke?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, anything can be funny in the right light.",
    "Choice 1" : "No, some subjects should not be joked about.",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, anything can be funny in the right light.",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you put more weight in science or faith?",
    "Answer" : "Science",
    "Choice 1" : "Faith",
    "Choice 2" : "Equally in both",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Science",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you think drug use with your partner can be a romantic activity?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Who are you most likely to reveal a dark, provocative secret to?",
    "Answer" : "My friends",
    "Choice 1" : "My partner",
    "Choice 2" : "A family member",
    "Choice 3" : "No one... I keep my secrets to myself.",
    "Prefer 1" : "My friends",
    "Prefer 2" : "My partner",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How frequently do you go out of your way to make others feel appreciated?",
    "Answer" : "About average",
    "Choice 1" : "About average",
    "Choice 2" : "Less than average / Never",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Way more than average",
    "Prefer 2" : "About average",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you okay with people who grow marijuana for their own personal use?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you date someone just for the sex?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How important is a potential match's sense of humor to you?",
    "Answer" : "Very important.",
    "Choice 1" : "Somewhat important.",
    "Choice 2" : "Not important.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "If you like someone a lot, do you usually ask them out?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you think big is beautiful?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which of the following best describes your typical demeanor?",
    "Answer" : "Cheerful!  I have a positive outlook.",
    "Choice 1" : "Meh. I have my ups and downs.",
    "Choice 2" : "Annoyed. The world sucks.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Cheerful!  I have a positive outlook.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Meh. I have my ups and downs.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you prefer sex rough or gentle?",
    "Answer" : "I enjoy both equally",
    "Choice 1" : "Gentle",
    "Choice 2" : "I enjoy both equally",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Rough",
    "Prefer 2" : "I enjoy both equally",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you get upset if your partner flirted in front of you?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you annoyed by people who are super logical?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Did you join OkCupid just so you could find people to have sex with?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "A college-level education is...",
    "Answer" : "Nice, but not mandatory",
    "Choice 1" : "Nice, but not mandatory",
    "Choice 2" : "Unnecessary",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Necessary",
    "Prefer 2" : "Nice, but not mandatory",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you believe that men should be the heads of their households?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which is scarier to reveal to a new partner?",
    "Answer" : "Neither",
    "Choice 1" : "Your body",
    "Choice 2" : "Neither",
    "Choice 3" : "Both equally",
    "Prefer 1" : "Your emotions",
    "Prefer 2" : "Neither",
    "Prefer 3" : "Both equally",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Being romantically approached by a stranger is:",
    "Answer" : "Usually more nice than annoying",
    "Choice 1" : "Usually more nice than annoying",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How often do you do things out of spite?",
    "Answer" : "Never.",
    "Choice 1" : "Sometimes.",
    "Choice 2" : "Rarely.",
    "Choice 3" : "Never.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Sometimes.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Rarely.",
    "Prefer 3" : "Never.",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy meaningless sex?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "What's your opinion of the phrase \"making love\" when it refers to sex?",
    "Answer" : "It's beautiful.",
    "Choice 1" : "It's hokey and overly sentimental.",
    "Choice 2" : "It refers to a very specific kind of sex.",
    "Choice 3" : "It's no better or worse than any other.",
    "Prefer 1" : "It's beautiful.",
    "Prefer 2" : "It refers to a very specific kind of sex.",
    "Prefer 3" : "It's no better or worse than any other.",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "On average, which best describes how often you GET WICKED DRUNK?",
    "Answer" : "Weekly / Bi-Weekly",
    "Choice 1" : "Weekly / Bi-Weekly",
    "Choice 2" : "Once every month or three.",
    "Choice 3" : "Seldom or never.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Twice a week or more",
    "Prefer 2" : "Weekly / Bi-Weekly",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Orgasms are clearly the most important part of sex.",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "I disagree.",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "In terms of sex, how experienced would your ideal mate be (with people other than you)?",
    "Answer" : "Slightly experienced",
    "Choice 1" : "Slightly experienced",
    "Choice 2" : "Moderately experienced",
    "Choice 3" : "Very experienced",
    "Prefer 1" : "Innocent (virgin)",
    "Prefer 2" : "Slightly experienced",
    "Prefer 3" : "Moderately experienced",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Is there such a thing as having had too many sex partners?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How do you feel about golden showers?",
    "Answer" : "Not for me, I'm a germaphobe",
    "Choice 1" : "Maybe, I could be convinced",
    "Choice 2" : "Not for me, I'm a germaphobe",
    "Choice 3" : "Can't, I might run for office one day",
    "Prefer 1" : "Not for me, I'm a germaphobe",
    "Prefer 2" : "Can't, I might run for office one day",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy giving oral sex?",
    "Answer" : "Love it!",
    "Choice 1" : "It's okay.",
    "Choice 2" : "Not so much.",
    "Choice 3" : "Gross!",
    "Prefer 1" : "Love it!",
    "Prefer 2" : "It's okay.",
    "Prefer 3" : "Not so much.",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you like to receive pain during sex?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, some",
    "Choice 2" : "No",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you allow your partner to kiss you after performing oral sex on you?",
    "Answer" : "Yes.",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes.",
    "Choice 2" : "No.",
    "Choice 3" : "It depends.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Allow? I enjoy it.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Yes.",
    "Prefer 3" : "It depends.",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you consider being in a relationship with someone who has had homosexual sex?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "I'm Not Sure / Depends how serious it was",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Receiving anal sex?",
    "Answer" : "I like it / I think I might like it",
    "Choice 1" : "I don't like it / I don't think I would like it",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "I like it / I think I might like it",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you ever consider having sex in a church?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "If you're in a relationship you expect will last for the rest of your life, is it important to you that it be the most satisfying sexual relationship you have ever had?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Group sex (with 3 or more people):",
    "Answer" : "It seriously interests me.",
    "Choice 1" : "It seriously interests me.",
    "Choice 2" : "I have little or no interest.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you fetish-friendly?",
    "Answer" : "Not sure/don't know what they really are.",
    "Choice 1" : "Never tried it, but I'm open-minded.",
    "Choice 2" : "Not sure/don't know what they really are.",
    "Choice 3" : "Ew!",
    "Prefer 1" : "Never tried it, but I'm open-minded.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Not sure/don't know what they really are.",
    "Prefer 3" : "Ew!",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Could you have respect for someone after having sex with them on the first meeting/date?",
    "Answer" : "Yes.",
    "Choice 1" : "No.",
    "Choice 2" : "Maybe, depending upon the circumstances.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Maybe, depending upon the circumstances.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you rather…",
    "Answer" : "avoid bondage all together",
    "Choice 1" : "do the tying",
    "Choice 2" : "avoid bondage all together",
    "Choice 3" : "sometimes be tied up, sometimes do the tying",
    "Prefer 1" : "avoid bondage all together",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Biting?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes",
    "Choice 2" : "Let's break skin",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How important is it for you to help give your partner an orgasm?",
    "Answer" : "Very important",
    "Choice 1" : "Somewhat important, but it's not everything",
    "Choice 2" : "Not very important",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Very important",
    "Prefer 2" : "Somewhat important, but it's not everything",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you turned on by sex in public?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, and I'm so down",
    "Choice 2" : "No",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you turned on by feet?",
    "Answer" : "Nope",
    "Choice 1" : "Sure, feet can be sexy sometimes",
    "Choice 2" : "Nope",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Nope",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you like to hear derogatory terms during sex?",
    "Answer" : "Sometimes, used sparingly it can be hot",
    "Choice 1" : "No, it's offensive",
    "Choice 2" : "Sometimes, used sparingly it can be hot",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you ever consider cutting a partner (who asked for it) in sexual play?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "Maybe",
    "Choice 2" : "No",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "You're in a new relationship and your partner admits that they have had 14 sexual partners. Does that sound like a lot to you?",
    "Answer" : "I guess, but It doesn't change how I feel.",
    "Choice 1" : "I guess, but It doesn't change how I feel.",
    "Choice 2" : "That seems like an average number.",
    "Choice 3" : "No, that's nothing.",
    "Prefer 1" : "I guess, but It doesn't change how I feel.",
    "Prefer 2" : "That seems like an average number.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "If your partner needed lovemaking to always be gentle, would you be fine with this?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Have you ever tried any sexual roleplaying?",
    "Answer" : "No, and it isn't going to happen. Ever.",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, on occasion. I have to be in the mood.",
    "Choice 2" : "No, but it sounds interesting.",
    "Choice 3" : "No, and it isn't going to happen. Ever.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, on occasion. I have to be in the mood.",
    "Prefer 2" : "No, but it sounds interesting.",
    "Prefer 3" : "No, and it isn't going to happen. Ever.",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How long can you go without sexual release?",
    "Answer" : "More than a day, less than a week.",
    "Choice 1" : "More than a day, less than a week.",
    "Choice 2" : "More than a week.",
    "Choice 3" : "I have never had sexual release.",
    "Prefer 1" : "A day or less.",
    "Prefer 2" : "More than a day, less than a week.",
    "Prefer 3" : "More than a week.",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you think you could ever enjoy being humiliated as part of a sexual experience?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which is better: sex without sleeping together or sleeping together without sex?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "Sleeping",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How confident are you in your sexual abilities?",
    "Answer" : "Super confident",
    "Choice 1" : "Confident",
    "Choice 2" : "Not really confident",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Super confident",
    "Prefer 2" : "Confident",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are some sex acts with consenting adults inherently wrong or immoral?  Assume no unusual risk of injury.",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you believe that regular sex is necessary in maintaining a healthy relationship?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "In your ideal sexual encounter, do you take control, or do they?",
    "Answer" : "I take control",
    "Choice 1" : "They take control",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you have a desire (even if it's secret) to take part in sexual activities involving bondage?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "Absolutely not.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "Absolutely not.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How much communication is ideal during sex?",
    "Answer" : "Just enough to get things right.",
    "Choice 1" : "Just enough to get things right.",
    "Choice 2" : "None. Shut up so I can concentrate.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you dump someone simply because they weren't good at sex?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Is it easy for you to achieve orgasm?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, any time the wind picks up",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, any time the wind picks up",
    "Choice 2" : "No, and I find it somewhat frustrating",
    "Choice 3" : "No, but don't worry, I'm enjoying myself",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, with skill and sometimes patience",
    "Prefer 2" : "Yes, any time the wind picks up",
    "Prefer 3" : "No, but don't worry, I'm enjoying myself",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which is a bigger deal for you?",
    "Answer" : "Telling someone you really care",
    "Choice 1" : "Oral sex",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Telling someone you really care",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "If your partner wanted you to say a specific phrase during sex, would you?",
    "Answer" : "Maybe, it would depend upon the phrase.",
    "Choice 1" : "No, I wouldn't.",
    "Choice 2" : "Maybe, it would depend upon the phrase.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, I'd say anything they want me to.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Maybe, it would depend upon the phrase.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you ever date someone that is HIV positive?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "I don't know",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How does the idea of being slapped hard in the face during sex make you feel?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "Aroused",
    "Choice 2" : "Nostalgic",
    "Choice 3" : "Indifferent",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy outdoor activities such as camping, hiking or fishing?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Does the idea of flipping a coin to make important life decisions appeal to you?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Is your ideal match well-off financially or at the very least someone who has high income potential?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, it's somewhat important.",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, it's somewhat important.",
    "Choice 2" : "No, it's not very important.",
    "Choice 3" : "No, it's not important at all.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, it's very important.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Yes, it's somewhat important.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you litter?",
    "Answer" : "Never",
    "Choice 1" : "Rarely",
    "Choice 2" : "Never",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Rarely",
    "Prefer 2" : "Never",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you be willing to date someone who plays video games almost every day, for at least 2 hours?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, but I don't like video games.",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, but I would not play that much.",
    "Choice 2" : "Yes, but I don't like video games.",
    "Choice 3" : "No.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, but I would not play that much.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Yes, but I don't like video games.",
    "Prefer 3" : "No.",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Your significant other is perfectly content with their minimum wage job and has no plans to look for more challenging/better paying work. Is this a problem?",
    "Answer" : "Somewhat, but it's their life.",
    "Choice 1" : "Somewhat, but it's their life.",
    "Choice 2" : "No, I don't mind.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, I wouldn't be able to tolerate that.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Somewhat, but it's their life.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Outside of work and school, how inclined are you to investigate something that interests you?",
    "Answer" : "Very inclined",
    "Choice 1" : "Somewhat inclined",
    "Choice 2" : "Not inclined",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Very inclined",
    "Prefer 2" : "Somewhat inclined",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy intellectual debates on topics like politics, religion, science, or philosophy?",
    "Answer" : "Sometimes.",
    "Choice 1" : "Sometimes.",
    "Choice 2" : "It's usually boring or annoying.",
    "Choice 3" : "I'm not smart enough.",
    "Prefer 1" : "I love to argue!",
    "Prefer 2" : "Sometimes.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which would you prefer your ideal match to be more into?",
    "Answer" : "Music",
    "Choice 1" : "Books",
    "Choice 2" : "Music",
    "Choice 3" : "Movies",
    "Prefer 1" : "Music",
    "Prefer 2" : "Movies",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Getting high on a date:",
    "Answer" : "sounds like fun",
    "Choice 1" : "is not for me",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Could you date someone who needs a great deal of alone time?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you pick up after yourself? Be honest.",
    "Answer" : "Always.",
    "Choice 1" : "Yeah, when I have the time.",
    "Choice 2" : "No, I live in filth.",
    "Choice 3" : "No, someone else does it for me.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Always.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Yeah, when I have the time.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Which is more important right now?",
    "Answer" : "Advancing in my career",
    "Choice 1" : "Finding a relationship",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you allow a pet to sleep on your bed?",
    "Answer" : "Yes.",
    "Choice 1" : "No.",
    "Choice 2" : "Maybe.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you attempt to conserve water, energy or other resources during your everyday life?",
    "Answer" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 1" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 2" : "No, I don't care",
    "Choice 3" : "No, it's my right to waste as much as I want",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, almost always",
    "Prefer 2" : "Sometimes",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Generally, do you enjoy being drunk?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "I don't know, because I've never been drunk.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you live with your parent(s)?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you an adventurous eater? Do you like to try new foods and cuisines?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, if it's not too strange.",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, if it's not too strange.",
    "Choice 2" : "On rare occasions/I don't know.",
    "Choice 3" : "No, yuck.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, all the time.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Yes, if it's not too strange.",
    "Prefer 3" : "On rare occasions/I don't know.",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy crude humor, dirty jokes, and the like?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, and I often try to push the boundaries!",
    "Choice 1" : "Usually, yes.",
    "Choice 2" : "Not in most cases, no.",
    "Choice 3" : "Absolutely not at all.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, and I often try to push the boundaries!",
    "Prefer 2" : "Usually, yes.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you consider living with a partner who does not want any pets?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How does your maturity level compare with most people your age?",
    "Answer" : "I'm average",
    "Choice 1" : "I'm average",
    "Choice 2" : "I'm less mature",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "I'm more mature",
    "Prefer 2" : "I'm average",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How important to you is being with family during holidays?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "Somewhat important.",
    "Choice 2" : "Not important.",
    "Choice 3" : "I have no family.",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Have you used psychedelic drugs (LSD, mescaline, peyote, etc.) or would you like to?",
    "Answer" : "No, I have not used them but I would try them.",
    "Choice 1" : "No, I have not used them and I would not try them.",
    "Choice 2" : "No, I have not used them but I would try them.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you like cats?  Would you consider owning a cat as a pet?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, I would love (or do own) a cat.",
    "Choice 1" : "I'm not too into them, but I wouldn't mind one.",
    "Choice 2" : "No, I dislike cats.",
    "Choice 3" : "I like them, but I'm allergic.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, I would love (or do own) a cat.",
    "Prefer 2" : "I'm not too into them, but I wouldn't mind one.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy exercise?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Does your partner have to be an active reader?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you rather play Scrabble, go out dancing, or get drunk?",
    "Answer" : "Booze",
    "Choice 1" : "Dancing",
    "Choice 2" : "Booze",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Dancing",
    "Prefer 2" : "Booze",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How important are academic achievements to you?",
    "Answer" : "Somewhat important.",
    "Choice 1" : "Somewhat important.",
    "Choice 2" : "Not important.",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Somewhat important.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Not important.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you ever eat something out of the trash?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "Maybe (if it's still good)",
    "Choice 2" : "No",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Maybe (if it's still good)",
    "Prefer 2" : "No",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How often do you try things (food, activities, music, whatever) that you've never tried before?",
    "Answer" : "Several times per week, or more.",
    "Choice 1" : "Several times per month.",
    "Choice 2" : "Several times per year.",
    "Choice 3" : "Rarely or never.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Several times per week, or more.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Several times per month.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you like wild parties?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you be comfortable being poor for the rest of your life?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How much do you go \"clubbing\" (out dancing in bars)?",
    "Answer" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 1" : "Sometimes",
    "Choice 2" : "Rarely",
    "Choice 3" : "Never",
    "Prefer 1" : "Lots",
    "Prefer 2" : "Sometimes",
    "Prefer 3" : "Rarely",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy long camping trips? (longer than 3 nights)",
    "Answer" : "I like to camp, but not long trips.",
    "Choice 1" : "I've never camped, but would like to.",
    "Choice 2" : "I like to camp, but not long trips.",
    "Choice 3" : "I love long camping trips.",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you like to go clubbing?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, I prefer to go with a date.",
    "Choice 1" : "Yes, I prefer to go with a date.",
    "Choice 2" : "Yes, I prefer to go with friends.",
    "Choice 3" : "No, I do not like to go clubbing.",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, I prefer to go with a date.",
    "Prefer 2" : "Yes, I prefer to go with friends.",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you hope to move around a lot?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, I'd like to live in many places",
    "Choice 1" : "No, I'm ready to put down roots",
    "Choice 2" : "I might move once or twice",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes, I'd like to live in many places",
    "Prefer 2" : "I might move once or twice",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you have a side hustle (sideline to bring in extra cash)?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Did you vote in the last election?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you use foul language?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Should partners know one another's passwords?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you describe yourself as sexy?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you believe in the power of prayer?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you smoke?",
    "Answer" : "Rarely",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "Rarely",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Could you date someone with no long-term goals?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you date someone who doesn't own a car?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Should wealthier people pay higher taxes?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you like to argue?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you like to watch sports on television?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you date someone who was always optimistic?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you currently employed?",
    "Answer" : "Yes, I have a fulltime job",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "I have a part-time job",
    "Choice 3" : "I'm a student",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Choose the better romantic activity:",
    "Answer" : "Kissing in a tent, in the woods",
    "Choice 1" : "Kissing in a tent, in the woods",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you strongly prefer to date someone of your own skin color / racial background?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "All",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "irrelevant"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you afraid of falling madly in love?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you totally anti-war?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you believe that everything happens for a reason?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you think taxes are justified?",
    "Answer" : "Yes",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "Yes",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Do you consider yourself to be a picky eater?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Are you afraid of death?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Would you ever seriously date someone half your age?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Can you name any ballet other than the Nutcracker?",
    "Answer" : "No",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "No",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  },
  {
    "Question" : "Should the government defund Planned Parenthood?",
    "Answer" : "skipped",
    "Choice 1" : "No",
    "Choice 2" : "I don't know",
    "Choice 3" : "",
    "Prefer 1" : "",
    "Prefer 2" : "",
    "Prefer 3" : "",
    "Importance" : ""
  },
  {
    "Question" : "How often do you masturbate?",
    "Answer" : "Once a day or more",
    "Choice 1" : "A few times a week",
    "Choice 2" : "A few times a month",
    "Choice 3" : "A few times a year or less",
    "Prefer 1" : "Once a day or more",
    "Prefer 2" : "A few times a week",
    "Prefer 3" : "A few times a month",
    "Importance" : "somewhat important"
  }
]